{
	"product": [
		{
			"pid": 100,
			"pname": "Tv",
			"price": 95000
		},
		{
			"pid": 101,
			"pname": "Computer",
			"price": 75000
		},
		{
			"pid": 102,
			"pname": "Laptop",
			"price": 45000
		},
		{
			"pid": 103,
			"pname": "Bike",
			"price": 255000
		}
	],
	"notproduct": [
		{
			"pid": 100,
			"pname": "Tv",
			"price": 95000
		},
		{
			"pid": 101,
			"pname": "Computer",
			"price": 75000
		},
		{
			"pid": 102,
			"pname": "Laptop",
			"price": 45000
		},
		{
			"pid": 103,
			"pname": "Bike",
			"price": 255000
		}
	],
	"JavaScript": [
		{
			"question": "Which of the following isn't a JSON type?",
			"optionA": "String",
			"optionB": "Object",
			"optionC": "Date",
			"optionD": "Array",
			"answer": "Date"
		},
		{
			"question": "Is whitespace matter in JSON?",
			"optionA": "No, it will be stripped out.",
			"optionB": "Yes, both inside and outside of strings",
			"optionC": "Yes, only within strings",
			"optionD": "Yes, only outside of strings",
			"answer": "Yes, only within strings"
		},
		{
			"question": "Who is the creator of JSON ?",
			"optionA": "Sergey Brin",
			"optionB": "Douglas Crockford",
			"optionC": "Liam Crockford",
			"optionD": "None of these",
			"answer": "Douglas Crockford"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of method JSON.parse()?",
			"optionA": "Parses a string from JSON to JSON2",
			"optionB": "Parses a string to integer",
			"optionC": "Parses a string to JSON",
			"optionD": "Parses integer to string",
			"answer": "Parses a string to JSON"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is the fastest JavaScript parser?",
			"optionA": "Acron",
			"optionB": "JSLint",
			"optionC": "Esprima",
			"optionD": "Traceur",
			"answer": "Acron"
		},
		{
			"question": "which of the following isn't create the object?",
			"optionA": "Object literals",
			"optionB": "Constructors",
			"optionC": "Object.create",
			"optionD": "Object Construct",
			"answer": "Object Construct"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the full form of JSON",
			"optionA": "JavaScripts Objection Notation",
			"optionB": "JavaScript Object Notation",
			"optionC": "JavaScript On Notation",
			"optionD": "None of these",
			"answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is JSON data?",
			"optionA": "Exchanging data",
			"optionB": "Non-exchanging data",
			"optionC": "Changing data",
			"optionD": "None of these",
			"answer": "Exchanging data"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is a JavaScript Compressor?",
			"optionA": "UgilifyJS",
			"optionB": "Esprima",
			"optionC": "Compressify",
			"optionD": "Acron",
			"answer": "UgilifyJS"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is the fastest JavaScript parser?",
			"optionA": "JSLint",
			"optionB": "Traceu",
			"optionC": "Esprima",
			"optionD": "Acron",
			"answer": "Acron"
		}
	],"TypeScript": [
		{
			"question": "Who developed and designed TypeScript?",
			"optionA": "Microsoft",
			"optionB": "Amazon",
			"optionC": "Oracle",
			"optionD": "TypeScript",
			"answer": "Microsoft"
		},
		{
			"question": "When was the first time TypeScript was made public?",
			"optionA": "December 2012",
			"optionB": "October 2012",
			"optionC": "October 2013",
			"optionD": "November 2013",
			"answer": "October 2012"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is the typing principle of typescript?",
			"optionA": "Gradual",
			"optionB": "Dynamic",
			"optionC": "Duck",
			"optionD": "All of the above",
			"answer": "All of the above"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is a filename extension for typescript?",
			"optionA": "tsx",
			"optionB": "nod",
			"optionC": "txt",
			"optionD": "tt",
			"answer": "tsx"
		},
		{
			"question": "Among which of the following computer programming language influenced the creation of typescript?",
			"optionA": "Java",
			"optionB": "JavaScript",
			"optionC": "C#",
			"optionD": "All of the above",
			"answer": "All of the above"
		},
		{
			"question": "The ...... Service powers the interactive TypeScript experience in Visual Studio, Vs Code, Sublime, the TypeScript playground and other editor.",
			"optionA": "Typescript language",
			"optionB": "TypeScript compiler",
			"optionC": "Typescript main",
			"optionD": "TypeScript method",
			"answer": "Typescript language"
		},
		{
			"question": "The following are backported features of typescript, except?",
			"optionA": "Classes",
			"optionB": "Methods",
			"optionC": "Modules",
			"optionD": "Arrow",
			"answer": "Methods"
		},
		{
			"question": "A typescript can be installed or managed through?",
			"optionA": "Void",
			"optionB": "Space",
			"optionC": "Nmp",
			"optionD": "Tag",
			"answer": "Nmp"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which Object Oriented Terms are Supported by Typescript?",
			"optionA": "Modulus",
			"optionB": "Interface",
			"optionC": "Classes",
			"optionD": "All of the above",
			"answer": "All of the above"
		},
		{
			"question": ".... are the way to organise code in typescript.",
			"optionA": "Modules",
			"optionB": "Classes",
			"optionC": "Method",
			"optionD": "Arrow",
			"answer": "Modules"
		}
	]
}